So I have it ironed and these two just meet; I don't even have to worry about struggling to make it meet.
Just do a little top sew.
And I'm just right next to the edge.
And don't even worry about back tacking because I'm going to show you how to attach it to the bag where all of this is hidden away.
I like to cut my threads, though.
So, I'm going to flip it over and I'm going to sew on this edge, right here, also.
And since I want to put four rows of stitching on it, I'm going to go ahead and look at it.
These guys are an inch apart, so I'm just going to go in about 3/8 of an inch; that should be about right, on each side.
Like I said, if you wanted to, you could just stay with doing these two or just one, it doesn't matter.
But I'm going to do my four.
And this one's a little easier; I don't have to measure it out; I just place it in between these two that I have.
Take a little look.
Yeah, I guess 3/8 was good; it's all 3/8 apart.
So, now that I have my strap, what I'm going to do next is show you how to finish off the drawstring.